let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "How to write a first order differential equation?",
        answer: "A.y'(x)+y(x)=F(x)",
        options: [
            "A.y'(x)+y(x)=F(x)",
            "B.y''(x)+y'(x)=F(x)",
            "C.y'(x)+y''(x)=F(x)",
            "D.none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "the integral :∫xy dxdy(0<x<1,1<y<2) equal :",
        answer: "D.3/4",
        options: [
            "A.5/4",
            "B.0",
            "C.1",
            "D.3/4"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "we give ∫xy dxdy with (0<x<1,0<y<2x):",
        answer: "A.Integration begins with Y",
        options: [
            "A.Integration begins with Y",
            "B.Integration begins with X.",
            "C.doesn't matter which variabl you start with.",
            "D.i don't know"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "the equation of the circle :",
        answer: "B.(x - x₀)² + (y - y₀)² = R²",
        options: [
            "A.(x - x₀)² + (y - y₀)² = 1",
            "B.(x - x₀)² + (y - y₀)² = R²",
            "C.x² + y² = 1",
            "D.x² + y² = R²"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "the equation of a ball is :",
        answer: "B.(x - x₀)² + (y - y₀)² + (z - z₀)² = R²",
        options: [
            "A.(x - x₀)² + (y - y₀)² + (z - z₀)² = 1",
            "B.(x - x₀)² + (y - y₀)² + (z - z₀)² = R²",
            "C.x² + y² + z² = R²",
            "D.x² + y² + z² = 1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "the homogeneous solution of:y'(x)+Dy(x)=F(x)",
        answer: "A.C*e^-∫D",
        options: [
            "A.C*e^-∫D",
            "B.C(x)*e^-∫D",
            "C.C*e^∫D",
            "D.none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The shortest war in history lasted only 38 minutes?",
        answer: "A.yes",
        options: [
            "A.yes",
            "B.i don't care bro ",
            "C.no",
            "D.?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "if delta=0 the homogeneous solution is :",
        answer: "C.(C1*x+C2)e^rx",
        options: [
            "A.C1*e^rx + C2*e^rx",
            "B.(C1*x+C2*x)e^rx",
            "C.(C1*x+C2)e^rx",
            "D.none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "if delta>0 the homogeneous solution is :",
        answer: "B.C1*e^rx + C2*e^rx",
        options: [
            "A.(C1*x+C2*x)e^rx",
            "B.C1*e^rx + C2*e^rx",
            "C.C1*e^rx - C2*e^rx",
            "D.none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "if delta<0 the homogeneous solution is :",
        answer: "C.e^ax[C1*cos(bx)+C2*sin(bx)]",
        options: [
            "A.e^bx[C1*cos(ax)+C2*sin(ax)]",
            "B.e^ax[C1*cos(bx)-C2*sin(bx)]",
            "C.e^ax[C1*cos(bx)+C2*sin(bx)]",
            "D.none of the above"
        ]
    }]